hello today um on the pixel shadow I am
مرحبا اليوم أم على ظل بكسل أنا
going to be filling in for mangafox 70 I
سوف يتم ملئه لـ mangafox 70 I
am more timer and mangle Fox 70 is sick
أنا أكثر توقيت وتذمر فوكس 70 مريض
but she's still in the game stick around
لكنها لا تزال في اللعبة تلتف حولها
this is it gonna be a great show welcome
هذا هو سيكون عرض عظيم الترحيب
to the pixel shadow I am Mortimer I am
إلى الظل بكسل أنا مورتيمر أنا
going to be filling in for mangafox 70
سوف يتم ملئه بـ mangafox 70
cuz she is sick she had to stay home but
كوز انها مريضة كان عليها البقاء في المنزل ولكن
she is still in the game and we are
انها لا تزال في اللعبة ونحن
going to be looking at some things like
سوف يكون النظر في بعض الأشياء مثل
parkour and builds that mangafox 70
الباركور ويبني أن مانغافوكس 70
hasn't shown off yet we are going to be
لم نستعرضها ولكننا سوف تكون
using some meskin to build some
باستخدام بعض المسكين لبناء بعض
machinery we are going to be showing off
الآلات التي سوف تكون الرياء
this house made by piston which is my
هذا البيت من المكبس الذي هو بلدي
other account and i like to use lava
حساب آخر وأنا أحب استخدام الحمم
underneath the floors because it looks
تحت الطوابق لأنها تبدو
cool
بارد
this is the downstairs I tried to make
هذا هو الطابق السفلي حاولت أن تجعل
it look like it was inside of the ground
تبدو كما لو كان داخل الأرض
and I haven't made much but the lava
وأنا لم أفعل الكثير ولكن الحمم
keeps leaking into this floor um but I
يبقي التسرب في هذه الكلمة أم لكن أنا
think I might have fixed that and I am
أعتقد أنني قد أصلحت ذلك وأنا
going to be making another floor which
سوف يكون صنع طابق آخر
the whole floor is going to be made out
الطابق بأكمله سوف يصنع
of lava this is just don't look out onto
من الحمم البركانية هذا هو فقط لا تنظر على
a big flat land that I found and we are
أرض مستوية كبيرة وجدتها ونحن كذلك
going to be looking at some park course
على وشك أن تبحث في بعض بالطبع الحديقة
that mangled Fox suddenly hasn't done
أن الثعلب المتشابك فجأة لم يفعل
and I like building my houses when you
وأحب بناء منزلي عندك
can jump instead of just being right
يمكن أن تقفز بدلاً من أن تكون على حق
over your head and I think my kitty fell
على رأسك وأعتقد أن بلدي كيتي سقط
into the lava wrong way so you get
في الحمم بطريقة خاطئة حتى تحصل عليه
upstairs so I'm gonna show you my house
في الطابق العلوي لذا سأريكم بيتي
it is very far away though very so I'm
أنها بعيدة جداً على الرغم من ذلك أنا
gonna go to this cottage which was also
ستذهب إلى هذا الكوخ الذي كان أيضا
made by me inside it is really dark
جعلها بداخلي مظلمة حقاً
because I accidentally turned off the
لأنني أوقفت عن غير قصد
lighting system and that means my
نظام الإضاءة وهذا يعني بلدي
lighting system doesn't really work
نظام الإضاءة لا يعمل حقا
anymore because I broke it sort of one
بعد الآن لأنني كسرتها من نوع واحد
open and I'll show you a lot about it so
مفتوح وسأريكم الكثير حول هذا الموضوع
this is blackouts cottage that he built
هذا هو كوخ انقطاع التيار الكهربائي الذي بناه
in my area what
في منطقتي ما
have you been doing this a farm ah stop
هل كنت تفعل هذا مزرعة آه توقف
Chuck die ha the stonework kiddies
تشاك تموت ها كيكيات الحجر
oh i should i just went around in a
أوه أنا يجب أن أذهب فقط في جميع أنحاء
circle how do i get into this place oh
دائرة كيف يمكنني الحصول على هذا المكان اه
yeah here's one of my entrance is to my
نعم هنا واحد من مدخلي هو بلدي
house it leads to this which is my porch
منزل يؤدي إلى هذا الذي هو راتبي
and inside is just my upstairs and then
والداخل هو فقط في الطابق العلوي من المنزل وبعد ذلك
there's another porch but I'm not done
هناك شرفة أخرى لكنني لم أفعل
yet and this is how you get my train
ومع ذلك ، هكذا تحصل على القطار الخاص بي
that leads to my snow house and this is
الذي يؤدي إلى منزل الثلج الخاص بي وهذا هو
just a storage room or something I don't
مجرد غرفة تخزين أو شيء لا أفعله
know what it is and over here is the
أعرف ما هو عليه وأكثر من هنا
stairs that go up to my higher ports and
السلالم التي ترتفع إلى موانئ أعلى و
it is right over top of the other parts
هو حق فوق الأجزاء الأخرى
that I just show you are you a notebook
أقوم فقط بعرض أنك مفكرة
well and I really would like to show you
حسنا ، وأود حقا أن تظهر لك
what my snow house looks like it is
ما يبدو عليه منزل الثلج الخاص بي
amazing need to grab a cart do I have
حاجة مذهلة للاستيلاء على عربة لدي
one no
واحد لا
oh this one was this year I'm gonna go
يا هذا كان هذا العام سأذهب
on this one so this leads to my snow
على هذا واحد وهذا يؤدي إلى الثلج بلدي
mansion I just called it slow house
قصر أنا فقط دعاها بطيئة البيت
because I didn't know that it was going
لأنني لم أكن أعلم أنها كانت مستمرة
to become a mansion I'm on the wrong
ليصبح قصر أنا على خطأ
really so that is blackouts house
حقا لذلك هو منزل انقطاع التيار الكهربائي
and we both know Jai model roller
ونحن على حد سواء يعرف بكرة نموذج جاي
coaster
السفينة
down the way
في الطريق
and this is my house
وهذا منزلي
this is just gonna go to
هذا مجرد الذهاب الى
on it protected area because I built
على المنطقة المحمية لأنني بنيت
this when I was pissed and so i had to
هذا عندما كنت غاضبة ولذا اضطررت إلى ذلك
find unprotected area which is this of a
العثور على منطقة غير محمية وهذا هو من
bedroom why is this here oh and this
نوم لماذا هذا هنا يا وهذا
leaves up upstairs which i'm not done
يترك في الطابق العلوي الذي لم أفعله
what's this for oh there's a camp out
ما هذا يا هناك معسكر
and this leads to downstairs so yeah
وهذا يؤدي إلى الطابق السفلي لذلك نعم
actually have to go down to make it
في الواقع يجب أن نذهب إلى جعله
upstairs which is cool it was a good
الطابق العلوي الذي كان رائعا كان جيدا
idea I don't know where this leads to
فكرة لا أعرف من أين يؤدي ذلك
this place is not finished yet what
هذا المكان لم ينته بعد
let's go a very weird and son go
دعونا نذهب غريب جدا وابنه يذهب
and watch out you don't want to fall
واحترس أنك لا تريد أن تسقط
down okay so this is a room that I
بانخفاض حسنا حتى هذه هي غرفة أنا
wanted to go into because it has my
يريد أن يدخل لأنه يحتوي على بلدي
teleporter that leads to all my stuff
teleporter الذي يؤدي إلى كل ما عندي من الاشياء
and I have more stuff than this so I'm
ولدي المزيد من الأشياء أكثر من هذا أنا
going to go to the door of my first
سوف أذهب إلى باب أول
build because that's the closest to
بناء لأن هذا هو الأقرب إلى
where I'm going ews device following me
أين أنا ذاهب جهاز ews يتبعني
so just follow this road which has been
فقط اتبع هذا الطريق الذي كان
briefed oh this I know this is my
اطلع على هذا أعلم أن هذا هو بلدي
mansion I'm asked this part up because
القصر سألت هذا الجزء بسبب
if part of my mansion is flooded so
إذا غمرت المياه جزءًا من قصري
flooded and all this
غمرت كل هذا
I'm going to
انا ذاهب الى
go over here I synced
اذهب الى هنا أنا مزامن
that right
هذا صحيح
no oh it's over here somewhere I
لا يا من هنا في مكان ما أنا
remember it being over here where you go
تذكر أنه يجري هنا حيث تذهب
but someone you're here or something my
لكن شخص ما أنت هنا أو شيء ما
even at the right place Oh
حتى في المكان المناسب أوه
however I see that place i just go all
ومع ذلك أرى هذا المكان أنا فقط أذهب كل شيء
the way over here oh oh my parkour is
الطريق هنا يا يا الباركور
over here yeah here it is so it has a
هنا نعم هنا كان الأمر كذلك لديها
lot of mechanics I might have to fix
الكثير من الميكانيكا قد أحتاج إلى الإصلاح
some of them cuz I'll like mechanics are
بعضهم كوز أنا أحب الميكانيكا هي
hard I'll tell you what ones I need to
من الصعب أن أخبرك ما الذي أحتاج إليه
fix this is just some type of story that
إصلاح هذا هو مجرد نوع من القصة ذلك
I made so you have to jump when you
أنا جعلت لذلك عليك القفز عندك
press this lever the door will open this
اضغط على هذه الرافعة الباب سيفتح هذا
is really hard to build here you'll have
من الصعب حقا بناء هنا عليك
to guess what wait yeah that's right you
لتخمين ما الانتظار نعم هذا صحيح لك
need to guess which button to press I'm
بحاجة إلى تخمين أي زر للضغط أنا
going to press this one ah that's what
الذهاب للضغط على هذا واحد آه هذا ما
that button does it just throws you off
هذا الزر يفعل ذلك فقط يرمي لك
and this is spun does the same thing but
وهذا هو نسج يفعل نفس الشيء ولكن
and this button opens up that place
وهذا الزر يفتح هذا المكان
that's cool Wow people will be able to
هذا بارد نجاح باهر والناس سوف تكون قادرة على
cheat by than that off and you jump here
الغش من قبل قبالة وتقفز هنا
some amazing this is here oh is that
بعض مذهلة هذا هنا يا هذا
supposed to be here I don't know
من المفترض أن أكون هنا وأنا لا أعرف
well this isn't so you go up here press
حسنا هذا ليس هكذا تذهب هنا الصحافة
this button and it will remove these I
هذا الزر وسوف يزيل هذه أنا
think these are not see it move them the
أعتقد أن هذه لا ترى أنها تحرك لهم
next button is really cool I let's get
الزر التالي رائع حقا دعنا نحصل عليه
rid of this the next button when you
تخلص من هذا الزر التالي عندما كنت
press it it will make stairs like that
اضغط عليه وسوف يصنع الدرج من هذا القبيل
and then you can go up the stairs around
ومن ثم يمكنك صعود الدرج
here here this build was really hard to
هنا هنا كان هذا البناء من الصعب حقا
build mobile so then you go in here this
بناء المحمول حتى تذهب هنا هنا
button will make that so that you can
سوف يجعل هذا الزر بحيث يمكنك
make it i'll show you how you have to do
جعلها سوف تظهر لك كيف يجب عليك القيام به
that oh how did I fall I thought okay
هذا كيف سقطت اعتقدت بخير
I'll just so you'll jump to here then
أنا فقط حتى سوف تقفز إلى هنا بعد ذلك
right here is pretty easy you just have
هنا سهل جدا لديك فقط
to do this oops and keep going and
للقيام بذلك عفوا والاستمرار و
unless that or else that will happen
ما لم يحدث ذلك أو غير ذلك
then you press that so that you can help
ثم تضغط على ذلك بحيث يمكنك المساعدة
us there's something wrong with this
لنا هناك شيء خطأ في هذا
yeah now this isn't supposed to be here
نعم الآن هذا ليس من المفترض أن يكون هنا
somehow it keeps doing that well that's
بطريقة ما يستمر في القيام بذلك بشكل جيد هذا
probably bumblebee and then here it will
ربما نحلة ثم هنا سوف
take away those
يسلب تلك
and then you keep on going nuts and so I
ثم تستمر في المكسرات وهكذا أنا
am going to build
سأبني
simple house and it's going to be over
منزل بسيط وانها ستكون على
water just because it would be cool and
الماء فقط لأنه سيكون باردا و
I like building above this overall
أنا أحب بناء فوق هذا العام
winner a lot but it's really hard
فائز كثيرًا ولكن من الصعب حقًا
especially when you make downstairs it's
خصوصا عندما تصنع الطابق السفلي
gonna be pretty much just going to be a
سوف يكون إلى حد كبير فقط سيكون
sensible house
منزل معقول
you can go much better health offense
يمكنك الذهاب إلى صحة أفضل بكثير
inland
في الداخل
it's going to be two blocks hi there are
انها ستكون كتل اثنين مرحبا هناك
a lot of people in my video I didn't
كثير من الناس في الفيديو الخاص بي لم أفعل
think that many people would come over
أعتقد أن الكثير من الناس سيأتون
to me so I'm gonna make a lighting
لي سأقوم بإضاءة
system so i am gonna take what block I
نظام لذلك أنا ذاهب لاتخاذ ما كتلة أنا
need one of these blocks and I do not
تحتاج واحدة من هذه الكتل وأنا لا
need a cart I can take one of these
بحاجة إلى عربة يمكنني أن أغتنم واحدة منها
blocks well I'm not going to do that yet
كتل جيدا أنا لن أفعل ذلك حتى الآن
if I'm going to make a one-block
إذا أنا ذاهب لجعل كتلة واحدة
lighting system like that so I'm going
نظام الإضاءة من هذا القبيل لذلك أنا ذاهب
to put that there that there I need a
لوضع هذا هناك أنني بحاجة إلى
piston sticky one and I have one so i
مكبس لزجة واحدة ولدي واحدة حتى أنا
don't need to search for one no you tube
لا تحتاج إلى البحث عن واحد لا أنبوب لك
to look this way
للنظر بهذه الطريقة
now i'm going to good obviously no one
الآن أنا ذاهب إلى الخير من الواضح أنه لا أحد
knows what I'm doing because the many
يعرف ما أفعله لأن الكثير
people here know how to build this and
الناس هنا يعرفون كيفية بناء هذا و
so this is let your only what I wanted
لذلك هذا هو السماح فقط ما أردت
to build now I'm going to just finish
لنبني الآن ، سأنتهي
off this part and obviously I make a
من هذا الجزء وبطبيعة الحال أقوم بعمل
store
متجر
they're so I am gonna get a lever if I
انهم حتى أنا ذاهب للحصول على رافعة إذا كنت
have one yeah I do need Anand hey wats
لديك واحد نعم أنا بحاجة إلى أناند يا حدى
stop destroying this i'm going to show
توقف عن تدمير هذا أنا ذاهب لإظهار
you how I'm gonna protect this
كيف سأحمي هذا
everything is stuff
كل شيء هو الاشياء
there now no one can vote here you can
هناك الآن لا أحد يستطيع التصويت هنا يمكنك
mangle Fox 70 is griefing wowzers haha
Mangle Fox 70 هو الحزن wowzers هاها
you shall never breathe again oh no go
يجب عليك أبدا أن تتنفس مرة أخرى أوه لا تذهب
away I don't need to see you oh no oh I
بعيدا لست بحاجة لرؤيتك يا لا أنا
thought I made it not be protected
أعتقد أنني لم تكن محمية
anymore so I have Mexican right here I'm
لم يعد لدي المكسيكي هنا أنا
going to place the lover right about
الذهاب لوضع الحبيب عن حق
here now hopefully no one uses it I
هنا الآن نأمل أن لا أحد يستخدم ذلك أنا
always do this so this lover will turn
دائما افعل هذا حتى يتحول هذا الحبيب
the light
الضوء
well that's just going to be so that's
حسناً ، هذا سوف يكون كذلك
just going to be her girls how does this
فقط ستكون بناتها كيف يفعل هذا
go see what block so I prize that powers
اذهب انظر ما كتلة لذلك أنا جائزة تلك القوى
out as well and when you press this it
خارج وكذلك عند الضغط عليه
should think this go like yep then when
يجب أن يفكر هذا الأمر مثل yep ثم متى
you undress it go like that oh do not be
خلع ملابسه تذهب مثل هذا يا لا يكون
oh I know I it's because I have to power
أنا أعلم أنني لأنني بحاجة إلى السلطة
the other one first
الآخر أولاً
I'm think that's what happened to miss
أنا أعتقد أن هذا هو ما حدث أن تفوت
my cottage
كوخ بلدي
now this will do the same thing will
الآن سوف يفعل هذا الشيء نفسه
power up this now I can make a lover
قوة هذا الآن يمكنني أن أجعل من عشيقها
here not connected it work
هنا غير متصل انها تعمل
it worked see now with the roof is
عملت رؤية الآن مع السقف
patched up then when I close it it still
مصححة عند إغلاقها لا يزال
has this block and when i press this mix
لديه هذه الكتلة وعندما اضغط على هذا المزيج
that so that's one thing that you could
هذا هو الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكنك فعله
build I actually learned this from a
بناء أنا فعلا تعلمت هذا من
Minecraft book but I didn't copy all of
كتاب ماين كرافت لكنني لم نسخ كل من
it cuz in mind test you don't have stuff
انها اختبار في عين الاعتبار ليس لديك الاشياء
like redstone repeaters so it's a little
مثل مكررات ريدستون لذا فهي صغيرة
bit different mmm so that's my kind of
ط ط ط مختلفة لذلك هذا النوع من بلدي
thing what are people doing I stopped
شيء ما يفعله الناس توقفت
doing it
فعل ذلك
hey turn this one looks the best cuz
مهلا تحويل هذا واحد يبدو أفضل كوز
spin w rats
تدور ث الفئران
so that's so awesome lighting system
لذلك هذا هو نظام الإضاءة رهيبة جدا
we're giving a different way thanks for
نحن نقدم طريقة مختلفة شكرا ل
watching a pixel shadow episode i hope
مشاهدة حلقة الظل بكسل أتمنى
you enjoyed it if i am able to make
لقد استمتعت بها إذا كنت قادرا على القيام بها
another video i can show you a lot of my
فيديو اخر استطيع ان اظهر لك الكثير من بلدي
other via builds goodbye
البعض عبر يبني الوداع